# **Brandon Robertson**

### Full Stack Developer

The Basin, Victoria brandonrobertson23@gmail.com

#### Bio

Brandon has a strong customer focus which has been developed through his previous roles. Outside of the workplace he will proactively use his time to write/produce music and relax while enjoying the latest video games. His interest in sales, and gaming have made him a strong team player while also creating a problem solving maniac and combining that with his passion for tech and programming make him a strong developer for any team.

## **Projects**

MERN Full Stack Assignment 2020

Ruby on Rails Full Stack Assignment 2020

Portfolio Assignment 2020

Ruby Command Line Assignement 2020

## **Employment History**

Reception / Manager Duties at Spoilt Rotten Jul 2014 — Dec 2019

Lilyfield, NSW Dogs

Picking / Packing / Sales / Warehouse Work Feb 2016 — Mar 2017

Five Dock, NSW at Car Care Products

Customer Service / Sales at Contact Centres Jan 2013 — Dec 2013

Sydney, NSW Australia

#### Education

Mar 2020 — Jan 2021 Coder Academy

Melbourne, VIC Diploma of Information Technology

Nov 2011 — Oct 2012 **TAFE** 

Ultimo, NSW Music Industry

Concord High School Jan 2009 - Dec 2012 Concord, NSW

**Higher School Certificate** 

Mooroolbark Secondary College Jan 2007 — Jan 2009

Mooroolbark, VIC **Higher School Certificate** 

#### References

Spoilt Rotten Dogs

Mario Pekar - Available Upon Request

Details

The Basin, Victoria

0431 301 705

Skills

JavaScript / MERN Stack

Ruby / Ruby on Rails

HTML5, CSS3 & SASS

Test-Driven Development

Version Control (via

GitHub)

Agile Methodologies

**Hobbies** 

Video Games, Writing and Producing

Music, Learning new Instruments and

Cooking

Social

GitHub -

brandon-robertson-dev

LinkedIn -

brandon-robertson-dev